Given an array A1,A2...AN, you have to print the size of the largest contiguous subarray such that
GCD of all integers in that subarray is 1.

Formally,
For a subarray Ai,Ai+1...Aj where 1 ≤ i < j ≤ N to be valid: GCD(Ai,Ai+1...Aj) should be 1. You have to print the size of the largest valid subarray.


If no valid subarray exists, output -1.

-----------------------------------------------------------------

It sounded a bit like finding the largest subsequence ... But the following insights need to be incorporated.

gcd(a, b, c) = gcd(a, gcd(b, c) )

And, gcd(1, n) = 1

This means that if there is a subarray with gcd 1, any array containing this array has gcd 1. 
So, if the array gcd is 1, the largest subarray with gcd 1 is the entire array.
If there is no subarray with gcd 1, 


    for(i = 1; i <= number_of_elements; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d", &number);

        array_gcd = (i == 1 ? number : gcd(array_gcd, number));
    }

    printf("%d\n",(array_gcd == 1 ? number_of_elements : -1));

--------------------------------

Note - For the inputs on the judge, the Euclidean algorithm was faster than the binary algorithm.