
Devu has an array A consisting of N positive integers. He would like to perform following operation on array.

Pick some two elements a, b in the array (a could be same as b, but their corresponding indices in the array should not be same). Remove both the 
elements a and b and instead add a number x such that x lies between min(a, b) and max(a, b), both inclusive, (i.e. min(a, b) ≤ x ≤ max(a, b)).
Now, as you know after applying the above operation N - 1 times, Devu will end up with a single number in the array. He is wondering whether it is
 possible to do the operations in such a way that he ends up a number t.

He asks your help in answering Q such queries, each of them will contain an integer t and you have to tell whether it is possible to end up t.
-------------------------------------------------

The final number can be reached if and only if it lies in between the minima and maxima of the array

    int no_of_queries, no_of_elements, i, minimum = INFINITY, maximum = -1, number_i, query_i;
    scanf("%d %d", &no_of_elements, &no_of_queries);

    for(i = 1; i <= no_of_elements; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d", &number_i);
        minimum = min(minimum, number_i);
        maximum = max(maximum, number_i);
    }

    for(i = 1; i <= no_of_queries; i++)
    {
        scanf("%d", &query_i);
        printf(minimum <= query_i && maximum >= query_i ? "Yes\n" : "No\n");
    }
